Words are upset, oh God, oh God, the heart is also upset, everything is scattered, scattered, scattered, the cold is upset, the silence is hidden, how do I ask, how do I ask, come, come
रूठी है शब्द रब्बा रब्बा दिल भी है रूठा सब कुछ है बिखरा बिखरा बिखरा सारू ठारूठा चिपनाइ चुप है लांजाल मोल कैसे वे लाजा मोल कैसे वे आ जा आ जा
Series
系列
Music is not silent, come, come, music
म्यूसिक नहीं चुप कर आ जा जा म्यूसिक
My dear, don't worry, I told you, I will handle everything
मेरा लोराया खैर तुम फिक्र मत करो मैंने कहा ना मैं सब संभाल लूँगा
Love
लव
You are so good
तुम कितने अच्छे हो
You take such good care of me, love me so much even knowing that I can't see, I am blind, you handle my home, my office, and support me in every way, thank you so much, oh there's no need to thank
मेरा कितना ध्यान रखते हो मुझे कितना प्यार करते हो ये जानते हुए भी की मैं देख नहीं सकती मैं अंधी हूँ मेरा घर संभाले हो मेरा ऑफिस सँभालते हो और मुझे हर तरह से कितना सपोर्ट करते हो थैंक यू सो मच अरे इसमें थैंक यू की क्या बात
we are not separate, if I don't handle your business, who will
है दोनों अलग थोड़ी है तुम्हारा बिज़नेस मैं नहीं संभालूंगा तो कौन संभालेगा
Come, I'll bring the final for you, sit
चलो तुम्हारे लिए फाइनल लेके आता हूँ बैठो
I'll bring the final for you
मैं तुम्हारे लिए फाइनल लेके आता हूँ
My name is doctor James
मेरा नाम डॉक्टर जेम्स है
I'm the eye specialist
मैं नेत्र विशेषज्ञ हूँ
it's our first time so don't worry I'm a friend of your husband
यह हमारा पहला समय है इसलिए चिंता मत करो मैं तुम्हारे पति का दोस्त हूँ
OK if you're ready let's head into the clinic
ठीक है अगर आप तैयार हैं तो क्लिनिक में चलें
Please have a seat
कृपया बैठ जाएं
Sorry but your husband will have to wait outside
माफ़ कीजिए लेकिन आपके पति को बाहर इंतज़ार करना होगा
I need to focus on my patient oh OK
मुझे अपने मरीज पर ध्यान केंद्रित करना है ओह ठीक है
thank you
धन्यवाद
OK zombies so how long have you not been feeling well
ठीक है ज़ॉम्बीज तो आप कितने समय से अच्छा महसूस नहीं कर रही हैं
10 years
10 साल
10 years I see and can you see these numbers on the blackboard here
10 साल मैं समझता हूँ और क्या आप यहाँ ब्लैकबोर्ड पर इन नंबरों को देख सकती हैं
OK look at your eyes
ठीक है अपनी आँखों को देखें
please let me take a quick
कृपया मुझे जल्दी से देखने दें
OK
ठीक है
thank you
धन्यवाद
One more check here how many fingers am I holding up
यहाँ एक और चेक है मैं कितनी उंगलियाँ उठा रहा हूँ
No no it's only one figure OK
नहीं नहीं यह केवल एक उंगली है ठीक है
I just need to check your temperature
मुझे सिर्फ आपका तापमान चेक करना है
Forgotten my thermometer
मेरा थर्मामीटर भूल गया हूँ
could you take your mask off please and open your mouth
कृपया अपना मास्क उतारें और अपना मुँह खोलें